http://www.fesmag.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyExamine the design, décor, and equipment and supplies packages in this award-winning monthly feature.
Advertisement
Resources
Privacy Policy
Foodservice Equipment & Supplies magazine appreciates your visiting our website. Your privacy and trust are important to us. We provide this notice to ensure that your expectations and our practices are aligned, and that you are aware of your choices regarding our use and disclosure of the information you provide to this site.
This Privacy Policy describes the policies of Foodservice Equipment & Supplies magazine and its parent company, Zoomba Group, LLC., regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of the following types of information:
Information obtained when you visit the Site.
Information obtained through e-mail communications with you related to the Site.
This privacy policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Your use of this Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to any action we take with respect to your information in compliance with this Privacy Policy.
We may change the terms of this Privacy Policy, so Users are encouraged to review this page from time to time. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy means that you accept the changes.
Information We Collect and How We Collect It
We require you to provide certain information about yourself when you register with this Site and when you request products and services. We also collect information when you participate in contests and surveys, when you respond to requests for feedback and when you submit postings to public areas of this Site (e.g., moderated discussions and bulletin boards).
The information we collect may include information from which you may be personally identified (“Personally Identifiable Information”), such as name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address, and certain business information such as employer name, occupation, job function, job title, purchasing preferences or history, and similar information. We also will collect credit card and related information when you request a product or service for which there is a charge. This Site only collects Personally Identifiable Information with your knowledge.
When you visit this Site, we may collect the IP address of your computer. We also use automatic data collection technology to record other information that identifies your computer and tracks your behavior on the Site. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information in this way, but if you provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, we may associate that information with the information that is collected automatically.
Automatic Data Collection through Cookies and Other Means
We may record information about your computer and/or track your activity while you are using our website or our other online products. For example, we may record how many times you click on a hyperlink, determine whether you visited our site from a particular Internet link or advertisement, or track your path through the site. This automatic data ("Automatic Data") collection may include but may not be limited to information collected by cookies, IP addresses, and transparent GIFs. We use this Automatic Data to report aggregated website activity and to better understand the needs of our users so we can make informed decisions regarding the content and design of the site. We may also use this Automatic Data to personalize your experience on our site. If you provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, we may combine and use the Automatic Data with the Personally Identifiable Information.
Some of our online content may be provided by third parties that may collect Automatic Data regarding your online activity. Information collected by third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and Zoomba Group is not responsible for their privacy policies, practices or content.
How We Use Your Information
We use Personally Identifiable Information collected on this Site for the following purposes:
To provide you with this Site and other products and services.
To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes regarding the Site.
To provide you with e-mail, fax and other notices (such as expiration and renewal notices) regarding your account and the products or services that you are receiving, and for billing and collection purposes.
For any other purpose disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent.
As otherwise specifically described in this Privacy Policy.
We also may use your information to better understand our Users and to improve our Site. For example, we may use this information to determine what portions of the Site are most popular and the demographics of our Users generally. Cookies and other User information also enable us to customize your experience on the Site. We may use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers or to administer our Site. We may also use IP addresses to help identify a User during a particular session and to gather data regarding use of the Site.
We may use the information you provide us to send you e-mail, fax and other communications on behalf of Zoomba Group and our affiliates. These communications may include e-mail newsletters that are relevant to this Site, as well as offers for other related services that we deem appropriate. All email newsletters will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of receiving future issues of the newsletter. All promotional offers will include an opportunity to opt out of receiving future promotions from the brand whose product/service is being promoted. Opt-out requests will be effective after a reasonable period of time for processing.
We also may use your information to send you e-mail and other communications on behalf of third parties. Each of these communications will include instructions for opting out of receiving future third party offers from us. You may also opt out of receiving third party offers from this Site at any time by sending an e-mail to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. with the subject line “opt out - third party.” Opt-out requests will be effective after a reasonable period of time for processing.
Opt-out requests are specific to particular products. If, for example, you unsubscribe from one Zoomba Group e-newsletter, you may still receive emails from us regarding other email, such as webinars or requests to complete surveys, all relating to Zoomba Group properties.
Our Disclosure of Your Information
We may disclose aggregated, anonymous statistics about many Users and other information that is not Personally Identifiable Information. We will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information except as follows:
Name and/or business name and title (but not information by which you may be contacted - i.e. name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address ) in representative lists of our magazine circulation and/or web site membership, but not for further use or dissemination by the recipient.
To third parties engaged to provide services under contractual requirement to keep Personally Identifiable Information confidential and use it only to perform the services.
Portions of this Site may be provided as “Premium” or “Sponsored” content. Premium or Sponsored content is made available to Users on the condition that we may share certain of the User's registration information with the Premium or Sponsored content's sponsors and advertisers. We will always disclose when you are registering or being provided with Premium or Sponsored content.
To other third parties to market their products or services under contractual requirement to keep Personally Identifiable Information confidential and use it only to market and provide their products or services. You may opt out of such disclosures by sending an e-mail to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. with the subject line: “do not disclose.”
To any successor pursuant to an asset sale, merger, consolidation, restructuring, reorganization, liquidation or other similar transaction involving Zoomba Group or this Site.
When we believe such disclosure is required by law, regulation or securities exchange requirement or for the protection of persons or property.
When disclosure is necessary to accomplish the purpose for which you provide it.
We may share any information (including Personally Identifiable Information) you provide with other Zoomba Group member companies for any uses consistent with those disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
Security
We use reasonable safeguards to protect Personally Identifiable Information we collect on this Site from unauthorized access, use, modification or disclosure. However, due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside of our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.
Right to Access and Change Information
You may view and update information that you previously submitted online to this Site by revisiting the registration or subscription form. Information updates will not be accepted if the request would conflict with legal requirements or if we believe it would result in incorrect information.
Links
This Site contains content, services, advertising and other materials that link to Web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. We encourage you to refer to the privacy policies, if any, of those sites.
California Privacy Rights
For purposes of California residents, this Privacy Policy pertains to all information collected online, including through this website. California law permits customers of Foodservice Equipment & Supplies who are California residents to request certain information regarding Foodservice Equipment & Supplies' disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us through the information provided below in "How to Contact Us."
Non-U.S. Residents
If you do not reside in the U.S. and are visiting our site, if you provide Personally Identifiable Information to us, it may be transferred to and processed on computers in the U.S. and other countries. Do not provide your Personally Identifiable Information to us if you do not want this information to be transferred outside of your country, or if the laws in your country restrict these types of transfers. Your provision of Personally Identifiable Information to us will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your provision of Personally Identifiable Information to us through this site means that you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Children's Privacy
We do not want to collect or maintain information from those under the age of 13. We do not permit children under 13 years of age to become registered users of our site. No part of our site is structured to attract anyone under 13. By using our site, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age.
Terms of Use
Your use of Zoomba Group's online products and sites constitutes your acceptance of the terms and conditions in this privacy policy as modified from time to time, including our collection and use of Personally Identifiable Information. If you are using the website on behalf of your employer, it means you are authorized to accept these terms on your employer's behalf.
The Privacy Policy may be amended as needed, so users are encouraged to review this page from time to time. The amended Privacy Policy will be effective upon posting on the site. Your continued use of Zoomba Group's online products and sites following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy means that you accept the changes and our use of your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the revised policy. Zoomba Group may, but is under no obligation to, provide you notice of such modifications to this Privacy Policy via email or other communication.
How to Contact Us
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding these privacy policies, please contact us:
Foodservice Equipment & Supplies® PO Box 156 Elmhurst, IL 60126
Toll Free: 800.630.4168 Toll Free Fax: 800.630.4169
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Follow Us On Social
Advertisement
FESFlix Featured Video
See More FESFlix Videos
Sponsored Content
Advertisement
Industry Calendar
Bar & Restaurant Evolve
November 2020 - April 2021Two sesions each monthhttps://events.barandrestaurantexpo.com/
Go to Calendar
Advertisement
FE&S Awards & Events
FE&S Webcasts On-Demand
Available 24/7
Need extra CEU credits before the year ends? Check out our full compilation of on-demand webcasts, each of which offer accreditation for various industry organizations.
Watch On-Demand
You May Also Be Interested In
Glueck to Lead ITW Food Equipment Group Cooking Lines
December 10, 2020
Markus Glueck will become group president, global cooking for ITW Food Equipment Group, effective Jan. 1, 2021. Earlier this month Glueck left RATIONAL USA, where he served as area vice president of North America for the combi oven manufacturer.
Read Article
Monticello Becomes SHFM President
December 10, 2020
The Society for Hospitality and Foodservice Management announced its 2020-2021 Board of Directors. Serving as SHFM president is Damian Monticello the senior manager, corporate hospitality services at GuideWell. In addition, Rob Gebhardt director, customer experience services for JLL, now serves as SHFM’s president-elect.
Read Article
Advertisement
Current Issue
View Our Current Digital Issue
Subscribe
Want to receive a FREE subscription to Foodservice Equipment & Supplies?
Enter First Name
Please let us know your First Name.
Enter Last Name
Please Enter Last Name
Your Email
Please let us know your email address.
Company
Please write a subject for your Company Name.
Continue Subscription Process
Subscribe to Our Newsletters
Keep up with the latest equipment and supplies entering the market with this FREE Newsletter.
Enter First Name
Please let us know your First Name.
Enter Last Name
Please Enter Last Name
Your Email
Please let us know your email address.
Company
Please write a subject for your Company Name.
Continue Subscription Process
Topics
PerspectivesProject ProfilesTrendsThe Latest News
Events
Dealer of the YearFoodservice Equipment and Design SummitIndustry EventsTour the TrendsWebcasts
Products
Beverage EquipmentCooking EquipmentPrep EquipmentSanitation and SafetyServing EquipmentRefrigeration, Storage & HandlingTabletop & Smallwares
Newsletter Archive
Flash NewsService InsightsThe SpecifiereMarketplace
Research
Distribution GiantsIndustry ForecastArchived Best in Class ReportsOperator Purchasing Study
Resources
About FE&SAccoladesSponsored ContentIndustry CalendarSubscribe to MagazineSubscribe to NewslettersMedia KitContact
Awards
Dealer of the YearDSR of the YearFacility Design Project of the YearHall of FameTop AchieversTabletop
Related Websites
rddmag.comzoombagroup.com
FESFlix
FOLLOW US ON SOCIAL
ABOUT US
Foodservice Equipment & Supplies (FE&S) is the one media source that connects equipment and supplies manufacturers and service providers with the full distribution channel including news, trends and best practices for foodservice equipment dealers, specifiers, operators, and supply chain partners.
Foodservice Equipment & SuppliesTopicsThe Latest NewsPerspectivesDSR of the MonthFoodservice by DesignThis Week In FoodserviceE&S ExtraProject ProfilesChain ProfileFacility Design Project of the MonthOn-Site ProjectsTrendsProductsGuide to…Beverage EquipmentCarbonated Beverage DispensersCoffee BrewersDraft Beer SystemsSlushies and SmoothiesCooking EquipmentFryersGriddlesOvensPanini PressesRangesRotisseriesSteamersSteam-Jacketed KettlesToastersTilting SkilletsPrep EquipmentBlendersBreadersChoppersJuicersMixersPortion ScalesProofing CabinetsSlicersSanitation and SafetyDishwashers and WarewashersDisposersOil FiltrationVentilationWater FiltrationServing EquipmentBuffetwareCountertop Condiment DispensersRefrigeration, Storage & HandlingBlast ChillersFood WellsIce Cream, Gelato and Soft-Serve Makers and FreezersIce MachinesHeated Display MerchandisersRefrigerationShelvingTabletop and SmallwaresCookwareCutleryDinnerwareGlasswareBrowse ProductsBeverage EquipmentBeverage DispensersCoffee BrewersDraft Beer SystemsSlushies and SmoothiesCooking EquipmentFryersGriddlesOvensPanini PressesRangesRotisseriesSteamersSteam-Jacketed KettlesToastersTilting SkilletsPrep EquipmentBlendersBreadersChoppersJuicersMixersPortion ScalesProofing CabinetsSlicersSanitation and Safety Equipment Dishwashers and WarewashersDisposersOil FiltrationVentilationWater FiltrationServing EquipmentBuffetwareCountertop Dispensers and OrganizersRefrigeration, Storage & HandlingBlast ChillersFood WellsIce Cream, Gelato and Soft-Serve Makers and FreezersIce MachinesHeated Display MerchandisersRefrigerationShelvingTabletop and SmallwaresCookwareCutleryDinnerwareGlasswareSubmit a ProductE&S DirectoryResearchDistribution GiantsIndustry ForecastOperator Purchasing StudyArchived Best in Class ReportsAwardsDealer of the YearDSR of the YearFacility Design Project of the YearHall of FameTabletop AwardsTop AchieversEventsDealer of the Year Awards GalaFoodservice Equipment and Design Global Thought Leadership Summit Industry CalendarTour the Trends201920182017201620152014Past WinnersWebcastsWatch
